dewalist.com 2017-12-04

# World Free Classified Ads Online | Community Classifieds | Dewalist

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy sets out our practices with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information in connection with www.Dewalist.com and other Dewalist site (the site). This Privacy Policy may be updated by us at any time by posting on the site without any prior notice. Also, this Privacy Statement may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between us and an individual from time to time. In this Privacy Statement, personal information means any information about an identifiable individual, including contact and demographic details, not including collective information or information regarding a group in summarised form.

Collection of Personal Information

The Site's uses an ad form that requires users to give us contact information (such as email address) and demographic information and other information that is used by us to provide services. We use the customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information that he or she has requested regarding the Site or regarding services offered by us. One of the express purposes of the Site is to gather contact information provided voluntarily by customers to be published either online or in print, as the case may be, and in connection with items that are for sale by customers. We have no control over who views online or print ads. Contact information provided may be used to contact customers when necessary. We use third party - Paypal to handle the customers financial information (such as account or credit card numbers) to promote products and services.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at the Site. We use this data to tailor each visitor's experience at the Site, showing the user content that we think he or she might be interested in, and displaying the content according to the users preferences. Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (such as email addresses) and demographic information (such as postal code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send users information about our products and services. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings (see the Opt-Out section below). We may use customer information for additional purposes that may be identified at or before the time that the information is collected. We also use information from customers for accounting and transaction completion purposes.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including email address) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Disclosure of Personal Information

We may disclose certain personal information as follows:

\- by publishing ads either online and/or in print, as the case may be, in connection with items that are for sale by customers

\- to third party service providers and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on our behalf,

\- to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences, or

\- to legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations.

\- by having your number listed on our site, you agree to receive communication from third parties who may wish to contact you through the site.

Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law.

Links

This Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.

Cookies and IP Addresses

We may use your IP address to identify you and your membership, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with our server, and administer the Site. The Site uses cookies to keep track of your membership tools and to make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. We use outside ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.

Corrections/Contact

Users of this Site may contact the Site to modify or correct any of their personal information that is under our control. An individual may also direct a written complaint regarding compliance with this Privacy Statement to us and, within a reasonable time upon receiving the written complaint, we will conduct an investigation into the matter, and we will take necessary measures to rectify the source of the complaint, as appropriate.

Opt-Out

When appropriate, users of the Site are given the opportunity to (i) opt-out of receiving communications from us, (ii) remove their information from our database, or (iii) elect to no longer receive services from us. If you wish to opt-out of receiving further communications, please [contact us](http://www.dewalist.com/contactus.php).

Security

We protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties. Our Paypal patrner use SSL to secure and encrypt the credit card data transmitted.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, our privacy practices in connection with this Site, or our collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your personal information in connection with this Site, please [contact us](http://www.dewalist.com/contactus.php).
